canvasondemand.com 2019-09-10

# Privacy Policy | Photo to Canvas - Canvas On Demand®

Effective Date: July 2019

This website is owned and operated by Circle Graphics, Inc., owner of the Canvas on Demand® brand ("Circle Graphics," "us," "we," and "our"). This Privacy Policy describes how Circle Graphics collects, uses and shares information that is collected about you through our websites, including www.greatbigcanvas.com, www.canvasondemand.com, www.circlegraphicsonline.com, www.cgproprints.com, www.eazl.com, www.canvasondemand.com/professional, www.cgsignlab.com, www.oohforgood.com, www.printsofgrace.com, www.inkush.com, www.signsofliberty.com, www.mycircleworks.com and the services offered on the websites (collectively the "Website"). It also describes how we protect the security of your information and how you can contact us about our privacy practices. "Personal Information" refers to information that personally identifies you, such as your name, mailing address, telephone number, email address or Internet Protocol (IP) address. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@circlegraphicsonline.com. CANVAS ON DEMAND® is a registered trademark of Circle Graphics, Inc.

This Privacy Policy provides information on:

_Changes to Our Privacy Policy_  
_Changes to Our Privacy Policy_  
_Information We Collect_  
_How We Collect and Use Your Information_  
_How We Share Your Information with Third Parties_  
_Legal Basis For Collecting Your Information_  
_Data Storage and Protection_  
_How We Protect Your Personal Information_  
_Making Changes To Your Personal Information_  
_GDPR Compliance_  
_Third Party Websites_  
_California Privacy Rights_  
_Questions and How to Contact Us_

**_Changes to Our Privacy Policy_**

We may make changes to the Privacy Policy from time-to-time. We will notify you of any material changes by sending you an email, posting a notice on the home page of the Website, or posting a notice in your account when you first login after we have made changes. If you receive notification of a change in our Privacy Policy, you should review the new Privacy Policy carefully to make sure you understand our practices and procedures.

**_Information We Collect_**

Circle Graphics collects information about you when you access the Website, communicate with us through the Website or social media, use Circle Graphics' web applications, or when you call or email us. We may also obtain information about you from our affiliates and business partners and from publicly available information. The information Circle Graphics may collect includes:

  * Personal Information such as name, mailing address, email, phone number and company name. You do not need to provide Personal Information in order to read the content portions of the Website.
  * Personal Information you provide us necessary to open an account or access our services, including usage information.
  * Other information you provide us or that may be obtained from third parties.

In addition, when you visit our Website, we may collect certain information by automated means, such as cookies, as described in more detail below. The information we may collect by automated means includes:

  * Information about the devices our visitors use to access the Internet, such as the IP address and the device, browser and operating system type.
  * Pages and URLs that refer visitors to our Website, and pages and URLs that visitors view after they leave our Website.
  * Dates and times of visits to our Website.
  * Information on actions taken on our Website (such as page views and site navigation patterns).
  * General geographic location (such as country and city) from which a visitor accesses our Website.
  * Search terms that visitors use to reach our Website.

The Website does not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals. Third party applications and plugins, such as social media integration, may treat DNT signals differently.

**No Information From Children Under Age 13**. This Website is not directed to children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will promptly delete that information. If you believe we have collected Personal Information from someone under age 13, please email us at privacy@circlegraphicsonline.com, or call us at (800) 557-2520. Prospective users between the ages of 13 and 17 can only use the Website and services under their parent's or legal guardian's supervision. If you are between the ages of 13 and 17, you, your parent, or your legal guardian may request that we remove any of your information in our database and/or opt-out from receiving communications from us. If you wish to do so, please email us at privacy@circlegraphicsonline.com or call us at (800) 557-2520.

**_How We Collect and Use Your Information_**

**Personal Information.** We use Personal Information primarily for internal business purposes, such as providing, maintaining, evaluating and improving the Website and the services offered through the Website, fulfilling requests for information, producing and shipping the products that you order, and providing customer support. For example, if you create an account with us, we will use the information that you provide us to communicate with you. Similarly, if you sign up to subscribe to a newsletter, we will use the email address you provide to send you the newsletters. Circle Graphics may use your Personal Information for targeted marketing and customer analysis by linking your information with third-party demographic and household data to provide a more personalized service.

**Google Analytics**. We use Google Analytics to help analyze how users use the Website. Google Analytics uses "cookies," which are text files placed on your computer, to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the Website (including IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors' use of the Website and to compile statistical reports on Website activity for Circle Graphics. For more information regarding how Google Analytics protects your data, please visit Google's website at www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html.

**Cookies**. A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters that is stored on your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that website to recognize your browser. Cookies may store unique identifiers, user preferences, and other information. When you visit our Website we store one or more "cookies" on your computer. You can set your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some website features or services may not function properly without cookies. We use cookies to improve the quality of the Website and services, including to store user preferences, to track user trends, and to provide relevant advertising to you.

**Pixel Tags**. We may use "pixel tags," also known as "web beacons," which are small graphic files that allow us to monitor the use of the Website. A pixel tag is a type of technology placed on a website or within the body of an email for the purpose of tracking activity on websites, or when emails are opened or accessed, and is often used in combination with cookies. A pixel tag can collect information such as the IP (Internet Protocol) address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the tag appears; the URL of the page on which the pixel tag appears; the time the page containing the pixel tag was viewed; the type of browser that fetched the pixel tag; and the identification number of any cookie on the computer previously placed by that server.

**_How We Share Your Information with Third Parties_**

**Subproccesors**. Circle Graphics uses data subprocessors to assist in providing its payment processing, analytics, storage, and advertising. A complete list of subprocessors Circle Graphics currently uses can be requested by emailing privacy@circlegraphicsonline.com.

**Disclosure to Unaffiliated Third Parties.** We may disclose your Personal Information to respond to legal requirements, to protect or enforce our rights and policies, to protect or enforce the rights of a third party, and to prevent harm to a person or as required or permitted by law (including, without limitation, to comply with a subpoena or court order).

**Disclosure to Third Party Service Providers and Online Partners**. We may contract with various third parties who help us provide, maintain, and improve the Website and the services. For example, we use a third party to process payments made to us, and may subcontract out production, fulfillment, analytics, reporting or other operations. We also contract with several online partners to help manage, monitor, and optimize our Website, and to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising, communications, and how visitors use the Website.

**Disclosure of Non-Personal Information**. We may disclose your de-identified information, in aggregate form, to potential strategic partners, advertisers, investors, customers, and others.

**Internet Advertising**. We may use third party service providers to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes on the Website. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our Website, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other websites to target advertisements for goods and services.

**Disclosure to Successors**. If we sell our business or one of our brands, we may transfer or sell your Personal Information to the new owner. In such a case, unless permitted otherwise by applicable law, your information would remain subject to the promises made in the applicable privacy policy unless you agree differently.

**Your Consent**. In addition to the sharing described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, we may share Personal Information with companies, organizations, or individuals outside of Circle Graphics if we obtain your consent to do so.

**_Legal Basis For Collecting Your Information_**

Circle Graphics collects and processes your data to provide the products and services you have requested or purchased, and to monitor, evaluate, and improve our business and the products and services we provide. We use your Personal Information to communicate with you concerning products and services you have requested or purchased, as well as other products and services we offer that you may be interested in. Circle Graphics may also have a legitimate interest in processing data to better understand the needs, concerns, and interests of its customers.

**_Data Storage and Retention_**

Your Personal Information is stored by Circle Graphics on its servers, and on the servers of the cloud-based database management services it engages, located in the United States. Circle Graphics retains data for the duration of the customer's business relationship with Circle Graphics, for the purposes indicated in this Privacy Policy, or for such other period as may be permitted or required by law, whichever is longest.

**_How We Protect Your Personal Information_**

**Personal Information**. We use industry standard physical, technical, and administrative security measures and safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of your personal information. When you enter sensitive information such as a credit card number on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using Transport Layer Security ("TLS") technology. However, since the Internet is not a 100% secure environment, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us.

**Website Content**. It is your responsibility to protect the security of your account and login information. Please note that content that you store or transmit through the Website or services, or e-mails and other communications you send to us, are not encrypted. You should not assume that your content will be kept private, and we strongly advise you not to communicate any confidential information through these means.

**_Making Changes To Your Personal Information_**

If you have questions about your Personal Information or need to update it, you can email us at privacy@circlegraphicsonline.com, or call us at (800) 557-2520. If you close your account, we will no longer use your online account information or share it with third parties. We may, however, retain a copy of the information for archival purposes and to avoid identity theft or fraud and for other legitimate business purposes. You can opt-out of receiving marketing or promotional e-mails from Circle Graphics by going to the account management section of the Website, or by using the opt-out or unsubscribe feature contained in the marketing or promotional e-mails.

We also provide you the opportunity to opt-out of having your information used for certain purposes. For example, if you purchase a product but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form.

**_GDPR Compliance_**

The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) provides certain rights to online users located in EU countries. You may withdraw your consent to processing of your Personal Information by sending an email to privacy@circlegraphicsonline.com. If you wish to confirm that Circle Graphics is processing your Personal Information, or wish to access Personal Information Circle Graphics may possess about you, please contact us at privacy@circlegraphicsonline.com. You may also request information about the purpose of the processing; the categories of Personal Information stored; who outside Circle Graphics might have received the Personal Information; what the source of the information was (if you didn't provide it directly to us); and how long it will be stored. You have a right to correct (rectify) the record of your Personal Information maintained by Circle Graphics if it is inaccurate. Subject to certain exceptions, you may request that Circle Graphics erase that Personal Information or cease processing it by emailing privacy@circlegraphicsonline.com. You may also request that Circle Graphics cease using your Personal Information for direct marketing purposes. When technically feasible, Circle Graphics will, at your request, provide your Personal Information to you or transmit it directly to another data controller. You also have the right to file a complaint with the data protection authority in your country of residence.

**_GDPR Compliance_**

The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) provides certain rights to online users located in EU countries. You may withdraw your consent to processing of your Personal Information by sending an email to privacy@circlegraphicsonline.com. If you wish to confirm that Circle Graphics is processing your Personal Information, or wish to access Personal Information Circle Graphics may possess about you, please contact us at privacy@circlegraphicsonline.com. You may also request information about the purpose of the processing; the categories of Personal Information stored; who outside Circle Graphics might have received the Personal Information; what the source of the information was (if you didn't provide it directly to us); and how long it will be stored. You have a right to correct (rectify) the record of your Personal Information maintained by Circle Graphics if it is inaccurate. Subject to certain exceptions, you may request that Circle Graphics erase that Personal Information or cease processing it by emailing privacy@circlegraphicsonline.com. You may also request that Circle Graphics cease using your Personal Information for direct marketing purposes. When technically feasible, Circle Graphics will, at your request, provide your Personal Information to you or transmit it directly to another data controller. You also have the right to file a complaint with the data protection authority in your country of residence.

Transferring Personal Data From the EU to the US.  In an attempt to comply with the GDPR's requirements, Circle Graphics collects and transfers your Personal Information to the U.S. or other countries outside the E.U. only: (1) consistent with an adequacy decision under Article 45; (2) pursuant to suitable safeguards; (3) with your consent; (4) to perform a contract with you; or (5) to fulfill a compelling legitimate interest of Circle Graphics in a manner that does not outweigh your rights and freedoms. If an adequacy decision for the transfer of Personal Information is not available or becomes invalid, Circle Graphics employs the standard contractual clauses in its agreements which can be obtained by emailing privacy@circlegraphicsonline.com.

**_Third Party Websites_**

You may be able to access third party websites directly from the Website. This Privacy Policy does not apply when you access third party websites. We cannot control how third parties may use any information you disclose to them, so you should carefully review the privacy policy of any third party website you visit before using it or disclosing your information to its provider.

If we disclose your information to a third party in a manner that is not set forth in this Privacy Policy, you will be notified so that you can make an informed choice about sharing your information with that third party.

**_California Residents_**

Under California's "Shine the Light" law, California residents who provide personal information in obtaining products or services for personal, family, or household use are entitled to request and obtain from us once a calendar year information about the customer information we shared, if any, with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of customer information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information for the immediately prior calendar year (e.g. requests made in 2018 will receive information regarding 2017 sharing activities).

To obtain this information, please send an email message to privacy@circlegraphicsonline.com with "Request for California Privacy Information" on the subject line and in the body of your message. We will provide the requested information to you at your e-mail address in response. Please be aware that not all information sharing is covered by the "Shine the Light" requirements and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response.

**_Questions and How To Contact Us_**

If you have any questions, concerns, complaints, or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy or otherwise need to contact us, please [Contact Us](https://www.canvasondemand.com/help/contact-us/https://www.canvasondemand.com/help/contact-us/), email us at service@canvasondemand.com, call us at (800) 557-2520, or contact us by US postal mail at the following address:

Circle Graphics Inc. (through its CANVAS ON DEMAND brand):  
10700 World Trade Blvd # 102,  
Raleigh, NC 27617
